export const CQuestion = [
    {
      question:
        "Who developed the bootstrap?",
      ans: 1,
      option: ["James Gosling", "Mark Otto and Jacob Thornton", "Mark Jukervich", "Dennis Ritchie"],
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to provide a responsive fixed width container?",
      ans: 2,
      option: ["All of the above", ".container-fluid", ".container", ".container-fixed"],
    },
    {
      question: "The plugin used to create a cycle through elements as a slideshow is -",
      ans: 2,
      option: ["carousel", "slideshow", "carousel", "None of these"],
    },
    {
      question: "The class in Bootstrap used to provide rounded corners to the image is",
      ans: 3,
      option: [".image-rounded", ".image-circle", ".img-circle", ".img-rounded"],
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to indicate the uppercased text",
      ans: 2,
      option: [".text-upper", ".text-capitalize", ".text-uppercase", ".uppercase"],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Is it true that the Bootstrap grid system works across multiple devices?",
      ans: 0,
      option: ["True", "False", ],
    },
    {
      question: "What is the default layout of the Bootstrap form?",
      ans: 2,
      option: ["a0Horizontal", " Vertical", "Inline", "None of the above"],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following class in Bootstrap is used to create a button as a link?",
      ans: 2,
      option: ["None of the above", ".btn-hyperlink", ".btn-link", ".btn-anchor"],
    },
    {
      question: "The class xs in Bootstrap is used for ",
      ans: 1,
      option: ["All of the above", "  phones  ", "tablets", "desktop"],
    },
    {
      question:
        "Which of the following statement is correct about the Bootstrap wells",
      ans: 0,
      option:[
        "All of the above",
        "By default, the size of wells is medium.",
        "Using .well-sm and .well-lg classes, we can change the size of wells.",
        "The .well-sm class is for small wells, and the .well-lg class is for large wells. And both classes should be used in conjunction with .well class.",
      ],
    },
    {
        question:
        "How many columns are allowed in a bootstrap grid system?",
        ans: 2,
        option:[
            "2", "12", "3", "5"
        ],
    }
  ];